export const questions = {
  sports: [
    {
      question: "Sport question 1",
      options: ["Sport 1", "Sport 2", "Sport 3", "Sport 4"],
      correctOption: "Sport 1",
    },
    {
      question: "Sport question 2",
      options: ["Sport 1", "Sport 2", "Sport 3", "Sport 4"],
      correctOption: "Sport 2",
    },
    {
      question: "Sport question 3",
      options: ["Sport 1", "Sport 2", "Sport 3", "Sport 4"],
      correctOption: "Sport 3",
    },
    {
      question: "Sport question 4",
      options: ["Sport 1", "Sport 2", "Sport 3", "Sport 4"],
      correctOption: "Sport 4",
    },
  ],
  music: [
    {
      question: "Music question 1",
      options: ["Music 1", "Music 2", "Music 3", "Music 4"],
      correctOption: "Music 1",
    },
    {
      question: "Music question 2",
      options: ["Music 1", "Music 2", "Music 3", "Music 4"],
      correctOption: "Music 2",
    },
    {
      question: "Music question 3",
      options: ["Music 1", "Music 2", "Music 3", "Music 4"],
      correctOption: "Music 3",
    },
    {
      question: "Music question 4",
      options: ["Music 1", "Music 2", "Music 3", "Music 4"],
      correctOption: "Music 4",
    },
  ],
  movies: [
    {
      question: "Movie question 1",
      options: ["Movie 11", "Movie 22", "Movie 33", "Movie 44"],
      correctOption: "Movie 11",
    },
    {
      question: "Movie question 2",
      options: ["Movie 111", "Movie 222", "Movie 333", "Movie 444"],
      correctOption: "Movie 222",
    },
    {
      question: "Movie question 3",
      options: ["Movie 1a", "Movie 2a", "Movie 3a", "Movie 4a"],
      correctOption: "Movie 3a",
    },
    {
      question: "Movie question 4",
      options: ["Movie 1", "Movie 2", "Movie 3", "Movie 4"],
      correctOption: "Movie 4",
    },
  ],
};
